[Butting into A Fight is Dangerous"]
(鳳仙)
これは これは 珍しいご客人で｡
My, my. What an unexpected guest.
The Harusame Seventh Division Commander,
(鳳仙)
春雨が第七師団団長… 神威殿｡
Kamui-dono.
(神威)やっぱり
地球のご飯は おいしいね｡
Earth food sure is good, Sir Housen.
鳳仙の旦那｡
春雨の雷槍と恐れられる
最強の部隊 第七師団｡
The Seventh Division... Harusame's feared and unrivaled Lightning Spear.
若くして その長にまで
のぼりつめた貴殿が➡
What business could one who has achieved so much at such a young age
こんな下賤な所に
何のご用ですかな？
have at my humble abode?
(神威)人が悪いですよ 旦那｡
You're too much, Sir.
第七師団 作ったのは旦那でしょ｡
You're the one who created the Seventh Division,
めんどうくさいこと
全部 ｵﾚに押しつけて➡
and then you left me with all the responsibilities...
自分だけ こんな所で悠々自適に
隠居生活なんて ずるいですよ｡
so you could retire here peacefully.
It's unfair.
As people age, their bodies and hearts change.
(鳳仙)人は老いれば身も心も渇く｡
What relieves the body is sake.
その身を潤すは酒｡
魂を潤すは女よ…｡
What relieves the heart is women.
ﾌﾌｯ 若いぬしには わからぬか｡
Perhaps you're too young to understand?
(神威)いえ わかりますよ｡
(鳳仙)ほう…｡
No, I understand.
Oh? So you've learned the taste of things other than food since I've last seen you?
しばらく会わぬうちに
飯以外の味も覚えたか ｸｸ…｡
酒か 女か？ 言え｡
Do you want sake? Women?
Just tell me.
じゃあ 日輪と ひと晩｡
In that case...
One night with Hinowa.
手土産も このとおり
用意してあるんです｡
As you can see, I've come prepared with a gift.
きっと喜んで
ｻｰﾋﾞｽしてくれるでしょ？
She'd be glad to serve me, don't you think?
ｲﾔですか？
日輪を誰かに汚されるのは｡
You don't want Hinowa to be tainted by someone else?
ｲﾔですか？
この子に日輪を連れ去られるのは｡
You don't want this boy to take Hinowa away?
ｲﾔですか？ 日輪と離れるのは｡
You don't want to be parted from Hinowa?
少し黙るがいい 神…｡
Be silent you-!
ﾊﾊﾊ…
年は とりたくないものですね｡
I wouldn't want to grow old...
あの夜王 鳳仙ともあろう者が
たった ひとりの女すら➡
It seems the one known as Night King Housen would be inept if it weren't for that one woman.
どうにもならない｡
女は地獄 男は天国の吉原？
Yoshiwara - a woman's hell, yet a man's paradise.
いや 違う ここは旦那｡
Well, not quite.
This place, Sir,
あなたが
あなたのためだけに創った桃源郷｡
is a paradise you built for yourself.
Kamui, I said to be silent.
(鳳仙)神威 黙れと言っている｡
誰にも相手にされない
哀れな おじいさんが➡
It's a prison where a pitiful old man whom nobody pays attention to...
かわいい人形たちを自分の元に
つなぎとめておくための牢獄｡
keeps cute dolls chained to his side.
聞こえぬのか 神威｡
Can you not hear me, Kamui?
(神威)
酒に酔う男は絵にもなりますが➡
A man drunk on sake is distinctive,
女に酔う男は
見れたものじゃないですな ｴﾛｼﾞｼﾞｲ｡
but a man drunk on a woman is just unsightly.  Right?
You old pervert?
(花魁)きゃ～…！
♪♪～
ｷｻﾏら ﾜｼを査定にきたのだろう｡
Did you bastards come to check up on me?
気づかぬとでも 思っていたか｡
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
元老の差し金だろう｡
They're orders from above, aren't they?
巨大な力を持つ吉原に
恐れを抱き始めたか ｼﾞｼﾞｲども｡
Have those old bastards finally begun to fear the great strength of Yoshiwara?
Is the Night King that hangs out in Yoshiwara becoming a nuisance?
吉原に巣食う
この夜王が じゃまだと｡
♪♪～
ぬしらに
この夜王 鳳仙を倒せると｡
Do you think you can defeat Night King Housen?
(阿伏兎)ｱﾝﾀといえども
春雨と正面から➡
Well, you may be correct, but you wouldn't want to take on Harusame head on, would you?
やりあう気には なれんだろう｡
It would be in your best interest to think before you act...
よく考えて
行動したほうが身のためだ｡
That would be a problem.
(神威)そいつは 困るな｡
そんなんじゃ ｵﾚのこの渇きは
どうすればいい…｡
If you do that, then what do I do about this thirst of mine?
女や酒じゃﾀﾞﾒなんだよ
ｵﾚは そんなものいらない｡
Women and sake don't cut it...
I don't need things like that.
They wouldn't be able to quench my thirst.
そんなもんじゃ ｵﾚの渇きは
癒えやしないんですよ｡
♪♪～
血…｡
Blood...
修羅が血…｡
The blood of Asura.
己と同等 それ以上の
剛なる者の血をもって 初めて…｡
Only when I'm with someone of equal or greater blood than mine,
ｵﾚの魂は潤う｡
does my soul cry out in ecstacy.
ｸｸｸ…｡
反目し 殺し合いを
演じたと聞いたが➡
I heard that you rebelled and tried to kill each other...
but you can't deny your blood.
血は争えんな｡
その眼は ﾔﾂの眼｡
Your eyes are just like his...
(鳳仙)その昔 夜王と呼ばれ
夜兎の頂点に君臨した わしに➡
Long ago...
When I, the Night King, reigned atop the Yato, only he ever refused to swear allegiance.
唯一 恭順せず➡
The man who challenged me all by himself...
たった一人で
挑んできた男…｡
(鳳仙)ぬしが父 星海坊主の眼｡
Your father,
Umibouzu's eyes.
三日三晩にわたる打ち合い
昨日のことのように覚えておるわ｡
I remember those three days and nights like they were yesterday.
わしと あれ程長く
対峙した者は ﾔﾂが初めて➡
He was the first to last that long against me.
決着がつかなかったのも
ﾔﾂが初めてであった｡
He was also the first person I was unable to settle a fight with.
そして…｡
And then...
((星海坊主:
あの… ｳﾝｺしたいんだけど))
Excuse me... but I need to take a dump.
(鳳仙)あんな幕切れも
初めてであった｡
It was the first time I had ever ended a fight like that as well.
神威 ｷｻﾏに
父が越えられるか？
Kamui, can you surpass your father?
I've surpassed him long ago.
もう とっくに越えているよ｡
(神威)家族だなんだと
つまらないしがらみに囚われ➡
Tied up by trifling issues like his obligation to his family and whatnot..
子供に
片腕を吹き飛ばされるような➡
A frail man like that who loses his arm to his own child...
脆弱な精神の持ち主に
真の強さは得られない｡
cannot obtain true strength.
(神威)旦那 あなたも
あの男と似ているよ｡
Sir, you are similar to that man.
外装は ｺﾞﾂくても
中身は酒と女しかない｡
Even though you look strong, there is nothing but sake and women inside you.
真の強者とは 強き肉体と➡
A true warrior needs a strong body in addition to a strong soul.
強き魂を兼ね備えた者｡
何者にもとらわれず
強さだけを求めるｵﾚに➡
I have nothing holding me back and only strive for power.
ｱﾝﾀたちは 勝てやしないよ｡
You guys can't beat me.
Keep talking, brat!
ぬかせ 小ﾜｯﾊﾟ!!
Don't do it, commander!
やめろ 団長!!
(月詠)すまぬ｡ わっちがもっと
早くに逃がしていれば｡
I'm sorry.
If only I had let you go sooner...
(銀時)
謝る必要なんてねえよ｡
There's no need to apologize.
(月詠)…行くのか？
Are you going?
(新八)
行かなきゃ 晴太君が死にます｡
If we don't go, Seita-kun will die.
行けば ぬしらも死ぬ｡
If you go, you'll die too.
夜兎が４人｡
軍隊一個あっても足りぬぞ｡
There are four Yato.
An entire army wouldn't be enough.
I have to do something about him.
(神楽)ｱｲﾂは 私が
なんとかしなきゃいけないね｡
誰がために行く？
晴太か 日輪か？
For whose sake are you going?
Is it for Seita? Hinowa?
ちょっくら 太陽
取り戻しに行ってくる｡
I'm going out for a bit to get some sun.
こんな暗がりに
閉じ込められてるうちに➡
The same one that everyone's forgotten about...
みんな忘れちまった太陽を｡
after living their lives out in this dump of a place.
どんな場所だろうとよ
どんな境遇だろうとよ➡
No matter where you are,
no matter how scared you are,
太陽は あるんだぜ｡
the Sun is there.
It's neither Hinowa nor Tsuji-chan's husband.
日輪でもねえ
辻ちゃんの旦那でもねえ➡
ﾃﾒｴの太陽がよ｡
Your sun...
雲に隠れて 見えなくなっちまう
こともよくあるがよ｡
is often covered by clouds.
それでも 空を見上げてりゃ➡
But if you continue to watch the sky, it will eventually make its way through the clouds.
必ず 雲の透き間から
ﾂﾗを出すときがやってくる｡
だからよ ｵﾚたちは
ｿｲﾂを見失わねえように➡
That's why... we must never lose sight of that.
空を仰ぎ見ることを
やめちゃいけねえんだ｡
We must never stop staring at the sky.
背筋しゃんとのばして
お天道様 まっすぐ見て➡
Stand up straight,
watch the heavens,
生きてかにゃ ならねえんだ｡
and continue to live your life.
Tell everyone you see who looks depressed...
しみったれたﾂﾗした
連中に言っといてくれ｡
空を見とけって…
あの鉛色の汚ねえ空に➡
to watch the skies.
In this filthy, lead-colored sky...
ｵﾚたちが ﾊﾞｶでかい太陽
打ち上げてやるってな｡
we're going to put up a ridiculously huge sun.
(月詠)悪いが断る｡
Sorry, but I refuse.
わっちも
共に行くからのう｡
Because I'll be going with you.
吉原との戦いに 吉原の人間
連れて行くわけにはいかねえ｡
We can't bring someone who belongs to Yoshiwara to a fight against Yoshiwara.
ﾃﾒｴ 裏切り者になるぜ｡
You'll become a traitor.
(月詠)言ったはずじゃ
わっちが護るのは日輪じゃ｡
I've told you already.
I protect Hinowa.
吉原に忠誠を誓ったことなど
一度もない｡
Not once have I sworn loyalty to Yoshiwara.
晴太を見殺しにするほうが
よほどの裏切りぞ｡
For me, it is even more treacherous to stand by and watch Seita die.
それに わっちも
人に頼るばかりじゃなく➡
Besides...
Instead of continuing to depend on others, I'd rather look for it myself...
自分で捜してみる気に
なったのさ｡
ﾃﾒｴの太陽というﾔﾂを｡
this so called sun you speak of.
帰るところなくなっても
知らねえぜ｡
Don't blame me if you have nowhere to return to.
(月詠)大丈夫じゃ｡
だって ぬしら➡
It's alright.
You're going to crush Yoshiwara anyway, right?
吉原を
叩き潰してくれるんじゃろう｡
♪♪～
(云業)団長 やめろ!!
Commander, stop it!
(云業)ｵﾚたちの目的を忘れたか？
(阿伏兎)よせ 云業！
Did you forget our objective?!
Stop, Ungyou!
(云業)団…｡
Com-
(神威)引っ込んでてよ…｡
今 楽しいところなんだ｡
Stay put.
I'm having fun right now.
ｼﾞｬﾏすると…➡
If you interfere again,
殺しちゃうぞ！
I'll kill you.
団長～!!
Commander!
言わんこっちゃねえ…｡
I told you...
あ～ また 始まちゃったよ…
団長の 悪いｸｾが…｡
The commander's bad habit's taken over him again.
♪♪～
(阿伏兎)ああなると
もう 誰にも止められねえ…｡
Once he gets like that, nobody can stop him.
♪♪～
(笑い声)
ぬぉ～っ!!
♪♪～
(神威)さすがは 夜王 鳳仙｡
As expected of Night King Housen, the man who once stood atop the Yato.
かつて
夜兎のいただきに立った男｡
おいそれと 下克上ってわけには
いかないようだね…｡
It seems like succeeding you isn't a simple task.
(鳳仙)ﾌﾝｯ！ 下克上？
笑わせるな！
Succeed me?
Don't make me laugh.
神威…
ｷｻﾏには 上も下も あるまい！
Kamui, you don't believe in hierarchies.
(鳳仙)あるのは 強いか弱いか…
ただ それだけ！
You only believe in the difference between the strong and the weak.
弱き者は 意にも介さんが➡
You don't bother yourself with the weak.
強き者は
たとえ それが誰だろうと➡
But against the strong, it doesn't matter who it is.
師のﾜｼであろうと 牙をむく！
You would even bare your fangs against your master.
それが
夜兎の血というものですよ｡
That's just how the Yato blood is.
(神威)こんな土の中に 安住し➡
While you were happily drowning yourself in sake and women,
酒と女に 溺れるうち➡
その血まで
渇いてしまいましたか…｡
did your blood dry out?
(神威)今の あなたに勝っても
おもしろくないや｡
Beating you as you are now would be no fun at all.
思い出してください…➡
Please try to remember...
the blood of Asura that flows through you.
己が中に流れる 修羅の血を…｡
黙れ！
Silence.
あなたの居場所は
こんな所じゃない｡
You don't belong in a place like this.
黙れと 言っているんだ！
I said to be silent.
(神威)あなたの居場所は…｡
You belong...
ｷﾞｬ～ｯ!!
♪♪～
(神威)そう…➡
That's right...
ｵﾚたちの居場所は 戦場ですよ｡
We belong on the battlefield.
♪♪～
うぉぉぉ～っ!!
(門番)まただ！
鳳仙様の部屋から…｡
There it is again. It's from Housen-sama's room!
やっぱり 私たちも行かないか？
(門番)もう 仲間が向かった！
Shouldn't we go check it out?
Our friends are already on the way.
こういう時ほど
警備を 怠ってはいかん！
It's at times like this that we can't loosen security.
隙をついて 曲者が
侵入するかもしれないだろう？
You don't know if an intruder will infiltrate through the gaps, right?
≪(月詠)そのとおりじゃ｡
Exactly.
(門番たち)頭！
Boss!
そこまでだ｡
２人とも 落ち着いてもらおう｡
That's enough. Both of you need to calm down.
んっ？
♪♪～
(阿伏兎)腕一本と １人で➡
My arm and his life were worth stopping your fight.
ｱﾝﾀらのｹﾝｶを止められれば
上出来だ｡
ｺｲﾂの命に免じて➡
Please don't let his death be in vain and forgive our commander's misconduct.
どうか
団長の不始末を 許してくれ｡
残り少ない 同族どうしで
殺し合うのは 寝覚めが悪い｡
Killing what few clan members we have left makes me uneasy.
ｵﾚたちゃ
ｱﾝﾀと 戦争しに来たんじゃねえ｡
We didn't come here to start a war with you.
よりよい関係を
築きに来ただけだ…｡
We came to strengthen our relationship.
いっそ この街が欲しいと
正直に言ったら どうだ？
Why don't you just admit that you want this town?
(阿伏兎)上も 怖いのさ｡
The higher-ups are scared as well...
夜王の怖さは➡
As one of us, we know your strength the best.
仲間だった ｵﾚたちが
いちばん知っている｡
じじいどもは
ｱﾝﾀが 裏切らないという証しが➡
The old men just want proof that you won't betray them.
欲しいのさ｡
たいした仲間だ｡
Quite the friends they are.
They're extorting a retired old man trying to peacefully live out the rest of his life.
隠居し 余生を送る老いぼれに
たかろうというのだからな…｡
興が覚めたわ…｡
旦那！
I've lost interest.
Sir...
(鳳仙)金でも商いでも
好きにするがいい｡
If money is what you want, take as much you want.
そんな くだらぬもの
ﾜｼは もう いらん｡
Things like that are worthless to me now.
だが この街…➡
However...
This town...
ﾜｼの国を
奪おうというのであれば…➡
If you try to steal my country,
ぬしら… 夜王の 真の姿
見ることになるであろう!!
I will show you the true strength of the Night King.
興ざめしたのは こっちだよ｡
I'm the one who has lost interest.
そんなに 自分の作った
おもちゃが大事か？
Is the toy you've made that precious?
ならば そのまま ここで
干からびて死んでゆけばいい｡
If so, you should just wither away here.
ｱﾝﾀは 殺すにも値しない｡
It's not even worth killing you.
干からびて死んでゆけ？
Wither away?
ﾌﾝ…
とうの昔に 干からびておるわ｡
I started withering away long ago...
日も浴びられぬというのに
どうして こんなに渇くものかな？
How have I shriveled so much when the Sun doesn't even reach me?
(門番)今まで どちらに？
(月詠)うむ｡
Where have you been this whole time?
Removal operations for the collapsed pipe.
崩壊したﾊﾟｲﾌﾟの 撤去作業にな｡
(門番)でも よかった｡
頭が来てくれれば 安心です｡
But I'm glad. We can relax now that you're here, Boss.
うむ… 鳳仙様のことは
わっちに任せておけ｡
Leave Housen-sama's matter to me.
ぬしらは ここの護りを頼む｡
(門番たち)はい！
I'll count on you guys to guard this place.
Roger!
いい？ 不審者は
一匹たりとも通しちゃ ﾀﾞﾒよ｡
Listen up. Don't let even one conspicuous person through.
If they're even a little suspicious, call 911.
ちょっとでも ﾋﾟﾝときたら110番よ｡
I give you permission.
ｱﾀｲが許可する｡
ﾍﾏしたら 承知しないからね｡
There won't be any mercy if you mess up.
(門番)頭！ 曲者です｡
Boss, they're suspicious.
いや 違う｡
それは あの… 新人りじゃ｡
Actually... no, they're not.
They're... um... new recruits.
新入り!?
こんな 怪しいﾔﾂらが!?
New recruits?!
These suspicious people are?!
ﾊﾟｰ子で～す！
I'm Paako.
ﾊﾟﾁ恵で～す！
I'm Pachie.
ｸﾞﾗ子で～す！
I'm Gurako.
(３人)３人合わせて
はちきれﾋﾟｰﾁ三太夫！
The three of us combined...
are the Three Bursting Peach Best Friends!
(門番)頭！ 曲者です｡
(月詠)いや 新入りだってば｡
Boss, they're suspicious.
No... I said they're new recruits.
大丈夫なんですか？
こんなの連れてって…｡
Are you sure you want to bring them?
鳳仙様のほうが はちきれますよ｡
Housen-sama is going to burst!
股間が？
んなわけねえだろ！
From his crotch?
No way!
鏡見てこい ｼﾘｺﾝ三太夫！
Look in a mirror, Three Silicon Best Friends!
こんな使えなさそうなﾔﾂらを
連れていくのは危険です！
Bringing such useless people is dangerous!
大丈夫よ～ どうせ
ちんほう様のことだから➡
It'll be okay. It's Chinhou-sama we're talking about.
また 女と一発
しけこんでるだけよ｡ 騒ぎすぎ｡
He's just slipping into another woman. Don't get so worked up.
(門番)ちんほう様って誰だよ？
鳳仙様！
Who's Chinhou-sama? It's Housen-sama!
どんな しけこみ方したら
あんな騒ぎになんの～!?
How would "slipping into someone" create a racket like that?!
いや 夜王とか呼ばれてんでしょ？
Well, he is called the Night King, right?
He's got to have a loaded bazooka, right?
そりゃ とんでもないﾊﾞｽﾞｰｶ
搭載してんでしょ？
(門番)そういう意味じゃねえよ！
That's not what it means!
新入りじゃが 腕は立つ連中じゃ｡
心配せずとも よい｡
They may be new recruits, but they're skilled.
You don't need to worry.
(門番)頭が そこまで言うのなら｡
If you say so, Boss.
お通りください｡
Please go through.
やりましたね｡ なんとか
ごまかせたみたいですよ｡
We did it. It looks like we fooled them!
(門番)お気をつけて
行ってくださいね｡
Please be careful...
死出の旅路を…｡
on the journey to your next life!
♪♪～
どうやら 猿芝居は
全部 ﾑﾀﾞだったようだな｡
It seems...
that whole act was a waste of time.
全部 お見通しってわけだ｡
They saw through everything.
(百華)頭… ｱﾝﾀが
賊に加担するとは…｡
Boss...
To think you would assist the intruders...
吉原を裏切ればどうなるか ｱﾝﾀが
いちばん知っているはずだ！
You should know best what happens when you betray Yoshiwara.
そうかい？
いったい どうなるってんだ？
Is that so?
What happens? Please tell us.
ぜひ お教え願いたいもんだ｡
こんなに たくさん集まって➡
There are so many of you gathered here, are you guys throwing a goodbye party?
お別れﾊﾟｰﾁｰでも
開いてくれるのかい？
銀さん ﾎﾝﾄにお別れです｡
Gin-san, it really is goodbye.
えっ 何が？
何がじゃねえだろ！
What is?
What do you mean "what is"? How many times have you been hit?!
何回 ぶっ刺さってんですか？
ｱﾝﾀは｡
ｵﾃﾞｺに ﾌﾞﾗｯｸﾎｰﾙでもあるんですか？
Is there a black hole on your forehead or something?!
え… 何が？
刺さってないよ 何も｡
What is? Nothing hit me.
刺さってただろ！ 今 明らかに➡
You were hit!
Your face is obviously turning red. You're embarrassed!
顔 赤くなってるだろ！
照れてるだろ！
おい いいかげんにしろよ｡
Oi, get it together.
決めるときは ﾊﾞｼｯと決めろよな｡
If you're gonna do it, do it right.
You were hit, right? You were obviously hit there, right?
刺さってたよね？ ｷﾐも明らかに
それ 刺さってたよね？
ﾌﾝ… 今から その調子じゃ
先が思いやられるわい｡
If you guys start out like that, I'm worried about what's to come.
ぬしら… そんなことでは➡
You guys... at this rate, you won't be able to beat the Night King in a hundred years!
100年かかっても
夜王には勝てんぞ！
突っ込みづらいんですけど｡
I'm just not going to comment.
そっとしといたほうが
いいよね あれ｡
I should probably leave her be, right?
知らないほうがいいよね？ あれ｡
It's better she doesn't know, right?
Death to traitors. That is the law here.
裏切り者には死を…｡
それが ここの掟！
その命をもってして 最後の掟
護るがいい!!
You should give up your life in order to protect our laws one last time!
嬉しいねぇ…｡
This is great...
Everybody working together to get the job done is more than a man like me deserves.
遊女総出の総仕舞たぁ
男冥利に尽きる｡
だが こう貧乳ばかりじゃ
興も冷めるってもんだ｡
However...
If you're all flat-chested, I'll lose interest.
女は やっぱり…｡
A woman needs...
爆乳でござんしょ！
giant melons!
Now then, let's kick off this party with a bang!
さぁ 楽しいﾊﾟｰﾁｰの始まりだ｡
(門番)うわぁ～!!
(爆発音)
You guys go get the children!
そっちは 子供のほうにまわれ！
私たちは 侵入者のほうにあたる！
We'll head towards the intruders!
たいした騒ぎだね｡
Quite the commotion.
ｱﾝﾀが起こしてくれた騒ぎより
ﾏｼだろ？
Better than the one you started.
なんだよ まだ怒ってんの？
What? You're still mad?
過ぎたことは忘れないと
長生きできないよ｡
If you don't learn to let go, you won't live a long life.
いやぁ 死んじゃったからね１人｡
Well, one of us is already dead.
なぁ ｱﾝﾀ 最初から鳳仙と
やり合うつもりだったんだろ？
Hey. You intended to mix it up with Housen from the start, didn't you?
ﾌﾌｯ ばれた？
(阿伏兎)
ばれたじゃねえよ ｽｯﾄｺﾄﾞｯｺｲ｡
Was it obvious?
"Was it obvious" my ass! Dammit.
おかげで駆け引きの道具も➡
Thanks to you, our bargaining chip got away during the confusion.
騒ぎの最中に
逃げちまう始末だ｡
(神威)あぁ あの子供のことか｡
Oh, you mean that boy? I totally forgot about him.
すっかり忘れてた｡
Getting away in the middle of that is quite a feat.
たいしたもんじゃないか
あのなかを逃げ出すなんて｡
先が楽しみだね｡
I look forward to his future.
(阿伏兎)ｹｯ 感心してる場合か｡
(神威)駆け引きなんか必要ないよ｡
Now's not the time for admiration.
We don't need a bargaining chip.
吉原が欲しいなら鳳仙の旦那を
殺してしまえばいいんだ｡
If we want Yoshiwara, all we have to do is kill Housen.
Are you an idiot?
(阿伏兎)ｱﾎか！ ｵﾚたちのせいで➡
If our actions cause a war between Harusame and the Night King,
春雨と夜王で
ﾄﾞﾝﾊﾟﾁ始めることになれば➡
the higher-ups are going to kill us!
元老にやられるのは ｵﾚたちだぜ｡
そのときは
元老もｵﾚが皆殺しにするよ｡
If that happens,
I'll slaughter the higher-ups too.
で そのあと あなた様は
海賊王にでもなられるんですか？
And after that, are you going to become the Pirate King?
(神威)それもいいかもねぇ｡
That sounds nice.
If I move up, I'll be able to meet people just as strong.
上に行けば
それだけ強いﾔﾂにも出会える｡
Yeah, yeah.
(阿伏兎)はいはい
志の高い立派な団長を持って➡
We're blessed to have a commander with such... great aspirations.
私どもは幸せですよ｡
God dammit.
ｺﾝﾁｸｼｮｳ！
Where are you going, Abuto?
どこ行くんだよ 阿伏兎｡
もう帰ろうよ｡
Let's leave already.
Then go.  Go home before that scary old man kills you.
(阿伏兎)帰れ 帰れ
怖いじいさんに殺される前にな｡
I can't just leave while I still owe Housen a favor.
鳳仙に貸し作ったまんま
帰れねえよ｡
We underlings are responsible for wiping the commander's butt.
我々 下々の者は団長様の尻拭い➡
いや 海賊王への道を
切り開きにでも行くとしまさぁ｡
No, maybe I'll go pave the way for the Pirate King.
ｹﾍﾍﾍ…｡
Good luck.
がんばってね～｡
これは煙玉！
ﾅﾒたﾏﾈを！
This is... a smoke bomb?
They're looking down on us. Are they saying they can't cut down women?
女は斬れぬとでも申すか！
あそこだ！
Over there!
ここで しばらく食い止める｡
I'll hold them back here for a while.
Go on ahead.
先に行きなんし｡
月詠さん！
Tsukuyo-san!
お前 死ぬ気あるか？
Do you want to die?
The boss needs to discipline her subordinates.
部下のしつけは頭がするさ｡
火種をよこせ｡
Hand over your pipe.
It'll be a problem if it disappears with you.
おめえと一緒に なくなられちゃ
困るんだよ｡
ｺｲﾂが使えなくなるだろう｡
I won't be able to use this.
最後になるやもしれん｡
It may be my last, so one last dra-
一服…｡
ﾀﾞﾒだ さっさとよこせ｡
No, hand it over.
銀さん
ﾎﾝﾄに置いていくつもりですか？
Gin-san, are you really going to leave her behind?
If you want to smoke that much, come back for it.
そんなに吸いたきゃ戻って来い｡
必ず戻って吸いに来い｡
Make sure you come back to smoke it.
If you don't make it quick, I'll drool all over it.
さっさと戻ってこねえと
しゃぶり倒すからな｡
ﾌｯ｡
Gin-chan...
(神楽)銀ちゃん…｡
Hurry, you guys go on too.
ぬしらも早く行け｡
何度も言わせるな｡
Don't make me repeat myself.
わっちが
身命を賭して護るは日輪のみ｡
Hinowa is the only person I'd ever give up my life for.
ぬしらごときを護るために
捨てる命など➡
I don't have enough lives to throw one away protecting the likes of you.
持ち合わせておらんわ｡
早く行け｡
Go quickly.
That's right.
《そう わっちは日輪を
命を賭して護る番人》
I'm a guard dog that lays down its life to defend Hinowa.
My sun...
《わっちの日輪を 吉原の日輪を｡
Yoshiwara's sun...
The guiding light of Yoshiwara.
吉原に光を導く日輪を…｡
I'm prepared to die.
死ぬる覚悟はできた｡
どこからなりとも来るがいい｡
Come at me however you may,
but I won't let even one of you pass me.
何人たりと
これより先には通さぬぞ》
日輪が番人 月詠 まいる！
The Guardian Dog of the Sun, Tsukuyo!
Here I go!
(神楽たち)どりゃ～！
Out of the way, dammit!
どけ ｺﾗｧ～！
急いで夜王のもとへ！
Hurry! To the Night King!
きっと そこに
晴太君がいるはずです！
Seita-kun must be there!
神楽ちゃん！
(阿伏兎)ｺｲﾂは驚いた｡
Kagura-chan!
What a surprise.
I was wondering who it was, so it's you guys.
誰かと思えば おたくらか｡
生きていたとは｡
I see you survived.
If the commander heard, he'd be elated...
団長が聞いたら喜びそうな連中だ｡
地球産にも
少しは骨のあるﾔﾂがいたってね｡
that there are Earthlings that actually have some muscle in them.
ｹｯ いよいよ お出ましか｡
You finally show yourself.
ひい ふう みい…
１人は もう殺ったとして➡
One, two, three.
Assuming I just killed that one, you're still missing one person.
それでも１人足りねえな｡
(神楽)おい
寝ぼけてんじゃねえぞ｡
Oi, stop daydreaming!
(神楽)誰が地球産あるか｡
Who's an Earthling?
こんな田舎もんたちと
一緒にすんなよ｡
Don't compare me to these country bumpkins.
I was born and raised a city girl.
こちとら 根っからのｼﾃｨｰ派ね｡
["Life I A Series Of Choices"]
They say life is really just one choice after another.
["Kamui's subordinate, Abuto, Kamui's younger sister, Kagura."]
["The two beasts fighting to the brink of death, awakens Kagura's Yato blood..."]
(ﾊﾘﾍﾞﾙ)１人で倒せないなら
みんなで倒せばいい｡
《ﾊﾘﾍﾞﾙ:次で… 倒す！》